Guide to the Duke Forest Records, 1931-ongoing UA.10.09.0001
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Accession UA2018.0036, 1
  - Folder 6: Loblolly Pine Field Records CP292-304 (Box 11)
  - Folder 6: Loblolly Pine Field Records CP305-317 (Box 11)
  - Folder 6: Loblolly Pine Field Records CP318-330 (Box 11)
  - Folder 6: Loblolly Pine Field Records CP331-343 (Box 11)
  - Folder 6: Loblolly Pine Field Records CP344-356 (Box 11)
  - Folder 6: Loblolly Pine Field Records CP357-369 (Box 11)
  - Folder 7: Loblolly Pine Field Records CP370-382 (Box 11)
  - Folder 7: Loblolly Pine Field Records CP383-395 (Box 11)
  - Folder 7: Loblolly Pine Field Records CP396-408 (Box 11)
  - Folder 7: Loblolly Pine Field Records CP409-421 (Box 11)
  - Folder 7: Loblolly Pine Field Records CP423-432 (Box 11)
  - Folder 7: Loblolly Pine Office Records CP344-356 (Box 11)
  - Folder 7: Loblolly Pine Office Records CP357-369 (Box 11)
  - Folder 8: Slash Pine, SE Coastal Plain II, New Trials, Planted Stands only (divider) (Box 11)
  - Folder 8: Slash Pine Plantations: Tex., Ala., La., Miss.: General (Box 11)
  - Folder 8: Slash Pine Plantations: Ga., Fla., S.C. Soil Site II (Box 11)
  - Folder 8: Slash Pine: Site Data: Tex., La., Ala., Miss. (Box 11)
  - Folder 8: Slash Pine Plantations: Tex., La., Ala., Miss. (includes volunteers: abandon later) (Box 11)
  - Folder 8: Slash Pine Plantations Site Curves; SE Coastal Plain and Gulf Combined (Box 11)
  - Folder 8: Slash Pine Plantations Gulf II; Planted stands only: not thinned; Stand data summaries (Box 11)
  - Folder 8: Slash Pine Plantations: SE Coastal Plain & Gulf Combined II; NC and SC: CP and Piedmont; BA and Trees per acre (Box 11)
  - Folder 8: Slash Pine Plantations: SE Coastal Plain & Gulf Combined II; Volume and Cu. Ft. per acre (Box 11)
  - Folder 9: Slash Pine Soil Site III (Box 11)
  - Folder 9: Loblolly pine: Effect of Thinning (Box 11)
  - Folder 9: Slash Pine III dx (Box 11)
  - Folder 9: Slash Pine III d1 (Box 11)
  - Folder 9: Slash Pine Soil Site III d3 (Box 11)
  - Folder 9: Slash Pine Soil Site III d4 (Box 11)
  - Folder 9: Slash Pine Soil Site III: d3 & d4 & odd drainages (Box 11)
  - Folder 9: Slash Pine Plantations Soil Site III: All drainages combined (Box 11)
  - Folder 9: Miscellaneous (Box 11)
  - Folder 10: Sand Pine Soil Site? (Box 11)
  - Folder 10: Loblolly Pine: Normal Eq. For Stand Variables Not Thinned; CP-G-Sandhills and Piedmont (Box 11)
  - Folder 10: Pine Plantations: General (Box 11)
  - Folder 10: Slash Pine Plantations: Volume Equations and Data (Box 11)
  - Folder 10: Slash Pine Plantations: Yield Equations (Box 11)
  - Folder 10: Slash Pine Plantations: Effect of Thinning (Box 11)
  - Folder 10: Slash Pine Plantations: Calculated Tables (Box 11)
  - Folder 10: Plantation Study: Slash Pine Site Curves (Box 11)
  - Folder 10: Direct Measurement (Box 11)
  - Folder 1: Loblolly Pine: BA & Trees per acre Equations; G: CP: Sandhills & Piedmont; Not thinned (Box 12)
  - Folder 1: Loblolly Pine Plantations: Volume Table Data & Preparation (Box 12)
  - Folder 1: Loblolly Pine: Volume per acre (not thinned); G: CP: Sandhills & Piedmont; V1 & V2 (Box 12)
  - Folder 1: Loblolly Pine Plantations: Yields of Unthinned Stands; Drainage d1, d2, d3, &d4 (Box 12)
  - Folder 1: Loblolly Pine Plantations: Yields of Unthinned Stands; Drainage dx (Box 12)
  - Folder 1: Loblolly Pine Plantations: Yields of Unthinned Stands; Savannah (Box 12)
  - Folder 1: Loblolly Pine Plantations: Yields of Unthinned Stands; Piedmont (Box 12)
    (ME-XE) = 17.5 and (ME-XE) = 7.5
  - Folder 2: Slash Pine Plantations; Planted trees only, not thinned; All data combined; BA & Trees per acre (Box 12)
  - Folder 2: Slash Pine Plantations; Planted trees only, not thinned; All data combined; Volume per acre (Box 12)
  - Folder 2: Yield tables: Slash Pine: d1, d2, & d3 (Box 12)
  - Folder 2: Yield tables; Slash Pine: d4 (Box 12)
  - Folder 2: Yield tables; Slash Pine: dx (Box 12)
  - Folder 2: Yield tables; Slash Pine: Savannahs (Box 12)
  - Folder 2: Yield tables; Slash Pine: Piedmont (Box 12)
  - Folder 2: Slash Pine Plantations: Yield Tables of Nov. 1961 (Box 12)
  - Folder 3: Slash Pine Plantations: Normal Eq. And Data for Stand Variable; Planted trees only: not thinned (Box 12)
  - Folder 3: Loblolly Pine: Effect of Thinning on Basal Area and No. of Trees (Box 12)
  - Folder 3: Loblolly Pine: Thinning Trials I; Average of Old Field and Not Old Field Data (Box 12)
  - Folder 3: Loblolly Pine: Effect of Thinning on Volume (1963) (Box 12)
  - Folder 3: Loblolly Pine: Thinning Trials II with Old Field Effect (Box 12)
  - Folder 4: Slash Pine: Effect of Thinning on Basal Area and No Trees (Box 12)
  - Folder 4: Slash Pine: Effect of Thinning on Volume (1963) (Box 12)
  - Folder 4: Slash Pine: Thinning Trials II with Old Field Effect (Box 12)
  - Folder 4: Discards: Not needed (Box 12)
  - Folder 5: Abandoned work (Box 12)
  - Folder 5: Slash Pine: Yield Tables for Unthinned Stands (1963) (without Old Field Effects) (Box 12)
  - Folder 5: Slash Pine: Not Thinned; Yield Table Calculations; Vol. per acre (V1 & V2) (Fall 1962) (Box 12)
  - Folder 6: Slash Pine: Preparation of Data for Bd. Ft. Analysis and Equations; Stand q.o. & Probits of Trees per Acre and Basal Area (Box 12)
  - Folder 6: Slash Pine: Yield Table Calculations (including Old Field Effects) (Box 12)
  - Folder 6: Slash Pine: Not Thinned; Yield Table Calculations; No. Trees, Basal area; Av. DBH (Fall 1962) (Box 12)
  - Folder 6: Slash Pine: Yield Tables for Unthinned Stands (with Old Field Effects) (1963) (Box 12)
  - Folder 7: Slash Pine (not thinned) Stand Tables (Fall, 1962) (Box 12)
  - Folder 7: Slash Pine Yield Equations of Unthinned Stands (Fall, 1962) (Box 12)
  - Folder 7: Slash Pine Notes (Sept., 1962) (Box 12)
  - Folder 7: Slash Pine Plantations: Height of Dominant Stand; Final; (a) All Regions, d1, d2, d3; (b) d4, (c) dx, (d) odd, & (e) Piedmont (Box 12)
  - Folder 8: Slash Pine Plantations: Volume Tables (cubic feet) (Box 12)
  - Folder 8: Slash Pine Plantations: Volume Tables (Intern. 1/4" kerf) (Box 12)
  - Folder 8: Unlabeled: T.S. Coile letterhead (Box 12)
  - Folder 8: Miscellaneous (unlabeled) (Box 12)
  - Folder 8: Plantation Studies: Miscellaneous Notes (Box 12)
  - Folder 8: Slash & Loblolly: Calculated SI & Confidence Limits (Box 12)
  - Folder 8: Slash & Loblolly: Combined Data & Equations (Box 12)
  - Folder 1: Loblolly Pine Soil-Site Equations (Final); SECP, Gulf, NC & SC, Sandhills (d1, d2, d3, d4) (Box 13)
  - Folder 1: Loblolly Pine: SECP & Gulf & Sandhills & NC + SC C D; Soil site: d1, d2, d3, & d4 combined (Box 13)
  - Folder 1: Loblolly Pine: CP & Gulf & Sandhills; Soil Site: (1) dx alone, (2) odd drainages (Final) (Box 13)
  - Folder 1: Loblolly Pine: Piedmont; Soil-Site Equation and Data (Final) (Box 13)
  - Folder 1: Loblolly Pine: Volume Tables in Board Feet (Box 13)
  - Folder 1: Loblolly Pine Plantations: Volume Tables (cu. ft.) (Box 13)
  - Folder 2: Loblolly Pine (notes; Sept., 1962) (Box 13)
  - Folder 2: Loblolly Pine: Yield Tables for Unthinned Stands without Old Field Effects (1963) (Box 13)
  - Folder 2: Loblolly Pine: Yield Table Calculations (including Old Field) (Box 13)
  - Folder 2: Loblolly Pine: Preparation of Data for Bd. Ft. Analysis and Equations; Prohits of Basal Area and No. Trees per Acre (1963) (Box 13)
  - Folder 3: Loblolly Pine: Not Thinned; Yield Table Calculations; No. Trees; Basal Area; Av. DBH; Ht. Of Dom. Stand (Fall, 1962) (Box 13)
  - Folder 3: Loblolly Pine: Not Thinned: Yield Table Calculations; Volume per Acre (v1 & v2) (Fall, 1962) (Box 13)
  - Folder 3: Loblolly Pine: Stand Tables, Not Thinned (Fall, 1962) (Box 13)
  - Folder 3: Loblolly Pine: Yield Tables for Unthinned Stands (including "Old Field" Effects) (1963) (Box 13)
  - Folder 3: Loblolly Pine: Yield Equations of Unthinned Stands (Fall, 1962) (Box 13)
  - Folder 4: Longleaf Pine Office Records L1-12 (Box 13)
  - Folder 4: Longleaf Pine Office Records L13-24 (Box 13)
  - Folder 4: Longleaf Pine Office Records L25-36 (Box 13)
  - Folder 4: Longleaf Pine Office Records L37-48 (Box 13)
  - Folder 4: Longleaf Pine Office Records L49-58 (Box 13)
  - Folder 4: Longleaf Pine Office Records L59-67 (Box 13)
  - Folder 4: Longleaf Pine Office Records L68-80 (Box 13)
  - Folder 4: Longleaf Pine Office Records L81-93 (Box 13)
  - Folder 4: Longleaf Pine Office Records L94-106 (Box 13)
  - Folder 4: Longleaf Pine Office Records L107-119 (Box 13)
  - Folder 4: Longleaf Pine Office Records L120-132 (Box 13)
  - Folder 5: Longleaf Pine Office Records L133-145 (Box 13)
  - Folder 5: Longleaf Pine Office Records L146-158 (Box 13)
  - Folder 5: Longleaf Pine Office Records L159-171 (Box 13)
  - Folder 5: Longleaf Pine Office Records L172-184 (Box 13)
  - Folder 5: Longleaf Pine Office Records L185-197 (Box 13)
  - Folder 5: Longleaf Pine Office Records L198-210 (Box 13)
  - Folder 5: Longleaf Pine Office Records L211-223 (Box 13)
  - Folder 5: Longleaf Pine Office Records L224-237 (does not include L-235) (Box 13)
  - Folder 5: Longleaf Pine Office Records L238-250 (Box 13)
  - Folder 6: Longleaf Pine Office Records L251-263 (Box 13)
  - Folder 6: Longleaf Pine Office Records L264-276 (Box 13)
  - Folder 6: Longleaf Pine Office Records L277-289 (Box 13)
  - Folder 6: Longleaf Pine Office Records L290-302 (Box 13)
  - Folder 6: Longleaf Pine Office Records L303-311 (Box 13)
  - Folder 6: Longleaf Pine Office Records L312-324 (Box 13)
  - Folder 6: Longleaf Pine Office Records L325-337 (Box 13)
  - Folder 6: Longleaf Pine Office Records L338-353 (Box 13)
  - Folder 6: Longleaf Pine Office Records L354-359 (Box 13)
  - Folder 7: Loblolly Pine Soil Site Study CP1-13 (Box 13)
  - Folder 7: Loblolly Pine Soil Site Study CP14-22 (Box 13)
  - Folder 7: Loblolly Pine Soil Site Study CP32-38 (Box 13)
  - Folder 7: Loblolly Pine Soil Site Study CP39-50 (Box 13)
  - Folder 7: Loblolly Pine Soil Site Study CP51-64 (Box 13)
  - Folder 7: Loblolly Pine Soil Site Study CP65-78 (Box 13)
  - Folder 7: Loblolly Pine Soil Site Study CP79-92 (Box 13)
  - Folder 7: Loblolly Pine Soil Site Study CP93-103 (Box 13)
  - Folder 7: Loblolly Pine Soil Site Study CP104-115 (Box 13)
  - Folder 8: Loblolly Pine Soil Site Study CP116-127 (Box 13)
  - Folder 8: Loblolly Pine Soil Site Study CP128-140 (Box 13)
  - Folder 8: Loblolly Pine Soil Site Study CP141-153 (Box 13)
  - Folder 8: Loblolly Pine Soil Site Study CP154-165 (Box 13)
  - Folder 8: Loblolly Pine Soil Site Study CP166-177 (Box 13)
  - Folder 8: Loblolly Pine Soil Site Study CP178-189 (Box 13)
  - Folder 8: Loblolly Pine Soil Site Study CP190-201 (Box 13)
  - Folder 8: Loblolly Pine Soil Site Study CP202-214 (Box 13)
  - Folder 8: Loblolly Pine Soil Site Study CP215-227 (Box 13)
  - Folder 9: Loblolly Pine Soil Site Study CP228-241 (Box 13)
  - Folder 9: Loblolly Pine Soil Site Study CP242-254 (Box 13)
  - Folder 9: Loblolly Pine Soil Site Study CP255-267 (Box 13)
  - Folder 9: Loblolly Pine Soil Site Study CP268-280 (Box 13)
  - Folder 9: Loblolly Pine Soil Site Study CP281-291 (Box 13)
  - Folder 9: Loblolly Pine Soil Site Study CP292-304 (Box 13)
  - Folder 9: Loblolly Pine Soil Site Study CP305-317 (Box 13)
  - Folder 9: Loblolly Pine Soil Site Study CP318-330 (Box 13)
  - Folder 9: Loblolly Pine Soil Site Study CP331-343 (Box 13)
  - Folder 9: Loblolly Pine Soil Site Study CP343-356 (Box 13)
  - Folder 10: Loblolly Pine Soil Site Study CP357-369 (Box 13)
  - Folder 10: Loblolly Pine Soil Site Study CP370-382 (Box 13)
  - Folder 10: Loblolly Pine Soil Site Study CP383-395 (Box 13)
  - Folder 10: Loblolly Pine Soil Site Study CP396-408 (Box 13)
  - Folder 10: Loblolly Pine Soil Site Study CP409-421 (Box 13)
  - Folder 10: Loblolly Pine Soil Site Study CP422-432 (Box 13)
  - Folder 10: Loblolly Pine Soil Site Study CP228-241 (not including 235, Slash Pine) (Box 13)
  - Folder 10: Loose papers (Box 13)
  - Folder 11: Loblolly Pine Office Records CP1-13 (Box 13)
  - Folder 11: Loblolly Pine Office Records CP14-22 (Box 13)
  - Folder 11: Loblolly Pine Office Records CP32-38 (Box 13)
  - Folder 11: Loblolly Pine Office Records CP39-50 (Box 13)
  - Folder 11: Loblolly Pine Office Records CP51-64 (Box 13)
  - Folder 11: Loblolly Pine Office Records CP65-78 (Box 13)
  - Folder 11: Loblolly Pine Office Records CP79-92 (Box 13)
  - Folder 11: Loblolly Pine Office Records CP93-103 (Box 13)
  - Folder 11: Loblolly Pine Office Records CP104-115 (Box 13)
  - Folder 11: Loblolly Pine Office Records CP116-127 (not including 117 pond pine) (Box 13)
  - Folder 12: Loblolly Pine Office Records CP128-140 (Box 13)
  - Folder 12: Loblolly Pine Office Records CP141-153 (not including 144 pond pine) (Box 13)
  - Folder 12: Loblolly Pine Office Records CP154-165 (Box 13)
  - Folder 12: Loblolly Pine Office Records CP166-177 (Box 13)
  - Folder 12: Loblolly Pine Office Records CP178-189 (Box 13)
  - Folder 12: Loblolly Pine Office Records CP190-201 (Box 13)
  - Folder 12: Loblolly Pine Office Records CP202-214 (Box 13)
  - Folder 12: Loblolly Pine Office Records CP215-227 (Box 13)
  - Folder 12: Loblolly Pine Office Records CP228-241 (not including CP235 slash pine) (Box 13)
  - Folder 12: Loblolly Pine Office Records CP242-254 (Box 13)
  - Folder 12: Loblolly Pine Office Records CP255-267 (Box 13)
  - Folder 12: Loblolly Pine Office Records CP268-280 (Box 13)
  - Folder 13: Loblolly Pine Office Records CP281-291 (Box 13)
  - Folder 13: Loblolly Pine Office Records CP292-304 (Box 13)
  - Folder 13: Loblolly Pine Office Records CP305-317 (Box 13)
  - Folder 13: Loblolly Pine Office Records CP318-330 (Box 13)
  - Folder 13: Loblolly Pine Office Records CP331-343 (Box 13)
  - Folder 13: Loblolly Pine Office Records CP370-382 (Box 13)
  - Folder 13: Loblolly Pine Office Records CP383-395 (Box 13)
  - Folder 13: Loblolly Pine Office Records CP396-408 (Box 13)
  - Folder 13: Loblolly Pine Office Records CP409-421 (Box 13)
  - Folder 13: Loblolly Pine Office Records CP422-432 (Box 13)
  - Folder 1: Pond Pine CP 43-64 Field Records (Box 14)
  - Folder 1: Pond Pine CP 61-77 Field Records (Box 14)
  - Folder 1: Long Leaf Pine L1-12 Field Records (Box 14)
  - Folder 1: Longleaf Pine L13-24 Field Records (Box 14)
  - Folder 1: Longleaf Pine L25-36 Field Records (Box 14)
  - Folder 1: Longleaf Pine L37-48 Field Records (Box 14)
  - Folder 1: Longleaf Pine L49-58 Field Records (Box 14)
  - Folder 1: Longleaf Pine L59-67 Field Records (Box 14)
  - Folder 1: Longleaf Pine L68-80 Field Records (Box 14)
  - Folder 1: Longleaf Pine & Loblolly L81-93 Field Records (Box 14)
  - Folder 2: Longleaf Pine & Loblolly L94-106 Field Records (Box 14)
  - Folder 2: Longleaf Pine L120-132 Field Records (Box 14)
  - Folder 2: Longleaf & Loblolly L133-145 Field Records (Box 14)
  - Folder 2: Longleaf PineL146-158 Field Records (Box 14)
  - Folder 2: Longleaf Pine L159-171 Field Records (Box 14)
  - Folder 2: Longleaf Pine L172-184 Field Records (Box 14)
  - Folder 2: Longleaf Pine L185-197 Field Records (Box 14)
  - Folder 3: Longleaf L198-210 Field Records (Box 14)
  - Folder 3: Longleaf L211-223 Field Records (Box 14)
  - Folder 3: Longleaf L238-250 Field Records (Box 14)
  - Folder 3: Longleaf Pine L251-263 Field Records (Box 14)
  - Folder 3: Longleaf L264-276 Field Records (Box 14)
  - Folder 3: Longleaf L277-289 Field Records (Box 14)
  - Folder 3: Longleaf L290-302 Field Records (Box 14)
  - Folder 3: Longleaf L303-311 Field Records (Box 14)
  - Folder 4: Longleaf Pine L312-324 Field Records (Box 14)
  - Folder 4: Longleaf Pine L325-337 Field Records (Box 14)
  - Folder 4: Longleaf Pine L338-353 Field Records (Box 14)
  - Folder 4: Longleaf Pine L354-359 Field Records (Box 14)
  - Folder 4: Pond Pine P1-13 Field Records (Box 14)
  - Folder 4: Pond Pine P14-26 Field Records (Box 14)
  - Folder 4: Pond Pine P27-89 Field Records (Box 14)
  - Folder 4: Pond Pine P40-42 Field Records (Box 14)
  - Folder 5: Longleaf Pine G2-19 Soil Site Study (Box 14)
  - Folder 5: Longleaf Pine G46-70 Soil Site Study (Box 14)
  - Folder 5: Longleaf Pine G71-83 Soil Site Study (Box 14)
  - Folder 5: Longleaf Pine G 85-99 Soil Site Study (Box 14)
  - Folder 5: Longleaf Pine G100-166 Soil Site Study (Box 14)
  - Folder 5: Longleaf Pine G167-181 Soil Site Study (Box 14)
  - Folder 5: Longleaf Pine G182-191 Soil Site Study (Box 14)
  - Folder 5: Longleaf Pine G192-204 Soil Site Study (Box 14)
  - Folder 5: Longleaf Pine G205-208-218 Soil Site Study (Box 14)
  - Folder 5: Longleaf Pine G221-238 Soil Site Study (Box 14)
  - Folder 5: Longleaf Pine G241-261 Soil Site Study (Box 14)
  - Folder 5: Longleaf Pine G263-299 Soil Site Study (Box 14)
  - Folder 5: Longleaf Pine G306-316 Soil Site Study (Box 14)
  - Folder 5: Longleaf Pine G317-329 Soil Site Study (Box 14)
  - Folder 5: Shortleaf Pine Plot # G139 Field Record (Box 14)
  - Folder 5: Shortleaf Pine Plot # G139 Office Record (Box 14)
  - Folder 6: Longleaf Pine G2-19 Office Record (Box 14)
  - Folder 6: Longleaf Pine G46-70 Office Record (Box 14)
  - Folder 6: Longleaf Pine G71-83 Office Records (Box 14)
  - Folder 6: Longleaf Pine G85-99 Office Records (Box 14)
  - Folder 6: Longleaf Pine G100-166 Office Records (Box 14)
  - Folder 6: Longleaf Pine G167-181 Office Records (Box 14)
  - Folder 6: Longleaf Pine G182-191 Office Records (Box 14)
  - Folder 6: Longleaf Pine G192-204 Office Records (Box 14)
  - Folder 6: Longleaf Pine G205-208 Office Records (Box 14)
  - Folder 6: Loblolly: Natural Stands Office Records (Box 14)
  - Folder 6: Loblolly Pine G1-20 Office Records (Box 14)
  - Folder 6: Loblolly Pine G21-30 Office Records (Box 14)
  - Folder 6: Loblolly Pine G31-40 Office Records (Box 14)
  - Folder 6: Loblolly Pine G41-56 Office Records (Box 14)
  - Folder 6: Loblolly Pine G58-67 Office Record (Box 14)
  - Folder 6: Loblolly Pine G-74-101 Office Records (Box 14)
  - Folder 6: Loblolly Pine G102-110 Office Records (Box 14)
  - Folder 7: Loblolly Pine G111-120 Office Records (Box 14)
  - Folder 7: Loblolly Pine G121-130 Office Records (Box 14)
  - Folder 7: Loblolly Pine G131-141 Office Records (Box 14)
  - Folder 7: Loblolly Pine G142-154 Office Records (Box 14)
  - Folder 7: Loblolly Pine G156-193 Office Records (Box 14)
  - Folder 7: Loblolly Pine G194-211 Office Records (Box 14)
  - Folder 7: Longleaf Pine G-Series Field Records (Box 14)
  - Folder 7: Loblolly Pine G1-20 Soil Site Study (Box 14)
  - Folder 7: Loblolly Pine G21-30 Soil Site Study (Box 14)
  - Folder 7: Loblolly Pine G31-40 Soil Site Study (Box 14)
  - Folder 7: Loblolly Pine G41-56 Soil Site Study (Box 14)
  - Folder 7: Loblolly Pine G58-67 Soil Site Study (Box 14)
  - Folder 7: Loblolly Pine G74-101 Soil Site Study (Box 14)
  - Folder 7: Loblolly Pine G102-110 Soil Site Study (Box 14)
  - Folder 7: Loblolly Pine G111-120 Soil Site Study (Box 14)
  - Folder 7: Loblolly Pine G121-130 Soil Site Study (Box 14)
  - Folder 7: Loblolly Pine G131-141 Soil Site Study (Box 14)
  - Folder 7: Loblolly Pine G142-154 Soil Site Study (Box 14)
  - Folder 7: Loblolly Pine G156-193 Soil Site Study (Box 14)
  - Folder 7: Loblolly Pine G194–211 Soil Site Study (Box 14)
  - Folder 7: Loblolly Pine G216-236 Soil Site Study (Box 14)
  - Folder 7: Loblolly Pine G237-255 Soil Site Study (Box 14)
  - Folder 7: Loblolly Pine G256-269 Soil Site Study (Box 14)
  - Folder 7: Loblolly Pine G270-283 Soil Site Study (Box 14)
  - Folder 7: Loblolly Pine G286-296 Soil Site Study (Box 14)
  - Folder 7: Loblolly Pine G297-307 Soil Site Study (Box 14)
  - Folder 8: Longleaf Pine G Series Field Records (Box 14)
  - Folder 8: Longleaf Pine G series Office Records (Box 14)
  - Folder 8: Longleaf Pine G series Soil-site-study (Box 14)
  - Folder 8: Southeastern Forest Experiment Station: Letter Mail to Dr. F. S. Coile: Field Procedure: Sand Pine (Box 14)
  - Folder 8: Longleaf Pine Field Records (Box 14)
  - Folder 8: Longleaf Pine Office Records (Box 14)
  - Folder 8: Slash Pine Field Records (Box 14)
  - Folder 8: Plots in Order from Filing Cabinet (Box 14)
  - Folder 8: Slash Pine Office Records (Box 14)
  - Folder 8: Slash Pine: Soil Site Study (Box 14)
  - Folder 1: Slash Pine S1- 13 (CP235) Soil Site Study (Box 15)
  - Folder 1: Slash Pine S14-26 Soil Site Study (Box 15)
  - Folder 1: Slash Pine S27-39 Soil Site Study (Box 15)
  - Folder 1: Slash Pine S40-52 Soil Site Study (Box 15)
  - Folder 1: Slash Pine S53-65 Soil Site Study (Box 15)
  - Folder 1: Slash Pine S66-78 Soil Site Study (Box 15)
  - Folder 1: Slash Pine S79-90 Soil Site Study (Box 15)
  - Folder 1: Slash Pine S91-103 Soil Site Study (Box 15)
  - Folder 1: Slash Pine S104-116 Soil Site Study (Box 15)
  - Folder 1: Slash Pine S117-129 Soil Site Study (Box 15)
  - Folder 1: Slash Pine S130-142 Soil Site Study (Box 15)
  - Folder 1: Slash Pine S143-155 Soil Site Study (Box 15)
  - Folder 2: Slash Pine S156-168 Soil Site Study (Box 15)
  - Folder 2: Slash Pine S169-181 Soil Site Study (Box 15)
  - Folder 2: Slash Pine S182-185 Soil Site Study (Box 15)
  - Folder 2: Slash Pine S186-198 Soil Site Study (Box 15)
  - Folder 2: Slash Pine S199, 213-215 Soil Site Study (Box 15)
  - Folder 2: Slash Pine S216-228 Soil Site Study (Box 15)
  - Folder 2: Slash Pine S229-231 Soil Site Study (Box 15)
  - Folder 2: Slash Pine S400-412 Soil Site Study (Box 15)
  - Folder 3: Loblolly Pine G series Field Records (Box 15)
  - Folder 3: Loblolly Pine G1-20 Field Record (Box 15)
  - Folder 3: Loblolly Pine G21-30 Field Record (Box 15)
  - Folder 3: Loblolly Pine G31-40 Field Record (Box 15)
  - Folder 3: Loblolly Pine G41-56 Field Record (Box 15)
  - Folder 3: Loblolly Pine G58-67 Field Record (Box 15)
  - Folder 3: Loblolly Pine G74-101 Field Record (Box 15)
  - Folder 3: Loblolly Pine G102-110 Field Record (Box 15)
  - Folder 3: Loblolly Pine G111-120 Field Record (Box 15)
  - Folder 3: Loblolly Pine G121-130 Field Record (Box 15)
  - Folder 4: Loblolly Pine G131-141 Except G139 which is shortleaf Field Record (Box 15)
  - Folder 4: Loblolly Pine G142-154 Field Record (Box 15)
  - Folder 4: Loblolly Pine G156-193 Field Record (Box 15)
  - Folder 4: Loblolly Pine G194-211 Field Record (Box 15)
  - Folder 4: Loblolly Pine G216-236 Field Record (Box 15)
  - Folder 4: Loblolly Pine G237-255 Field Record (Box 15)
  - Folder 4: Loblolly Pine G256-269 Field Record (Box 15)
  - Folder 4: Loblolly Pine G270-283 Field Record (Box 15)
  - Folder 4: Loblolly Pine G286-296 Field Record (Box 15)
  - Folder 4: Loblolly Pine G297-307 Field Record (Box 15)
  - Folder 5: Loblolly Pine G series Soil Site Study (Box 15)
  - Folder 5: Spring 1948 Longleaf Pine Soil Data (Bound in Twine) (Box 15)
  - Folder 6: Slash Pine Plantations Plots 4-28 Office Records 31 Not Thinned SECP (Box 15)
  - Folder 6: Slash Pine Plantations Plots 29-55 Office Records 32 Not Thinned SECP (Box 15)
  - Folder 6: Slash pine Plantations Plots 56-80 Office Records 33 SECP Not Thinned (Box 15)
  - Folder 6: Slash Pine Plantations Plots 81-105 Office Records 34 Not Thinned SECP (Box 15)
  - Folder 6: Slash Pine Plantations Plots 106-139 Office Records 35 Not Thinned SECP (Box 15)
  - Folder 6: Slash Pine Plantations Plots 134-150 Office Records 36 Not Thinned SECP (Box 15)
  - Folder 6: Slash Pine Plantations Plots 159-180 Office Records 37 Not Thinned SECP (Box 15)
  - Folder 6: Slash Pine Plantations Plots 181-202 Office Records 38 Not Thinned SECP (Box 15)
  - Folder 7: Slash Pine Plantations Plots 209-232 Office Records 39 Not Thinned SECP (Box 15)
  - Folder 7: Slash Pine Plantations Plots 235-254 Office Records 40 Not Thinned SECP (Box 15)
  - Folder 7: South East Coastal Plain Slash Plot 20-195 41 Thinned (Box 15)
  - Folder 7: South East Coastal Plain Slash 42 Plot 196-256 Thinned (Box 15)
  - Folder 7: Miscellaenous (Box 15)
  - Folder 8 (Bound by Yellow Marking Tape): Longleaf Pine Soil Site Study L1-12 (Box 15)